<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Labnotes on K8S Operators Over EZ</title>
    <link>http://localhost/labnotes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Labnotes on K8S Operators Over EZ</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="http://localhost/labnotes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost/labnotes/lab-requirements/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost/labnotes/lab-requirements/</guid>
      <description>To run the labs and scripts in this guide, you will need the following:
 An accessible kubernetes cluster with sufficient privileges kubectl kubectx/kubens operator-sdk &amp;gt;= 1.0.0 kustomize golang make - build uitlity a shell environment (i.e. bash, zsh) a text editor  Ensure that all of the above CLI executables are availabe in your PATH environment variable.
K8S Development Cluster Suggestions If you do not have access to a cluster, there are options to allow you to run a cluster locally:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost/labnotes/specifications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost/labnotes/specifications/</guid>
      <description>Story - BDD/Gherkin TITLE: Overeasy Operator Requirements
  DESCRIPTION
 AS A: Developer I WANT: An Operator with a single busybox pod that logs a user specified message and shuts down after a user specified amount of time. If a duration or message are not specified, then both will be supplied by a REST API call. SO THAT: I can demonstrate the encapsulation of operational knowlege, leveraging the Operator Design Pattern.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost/labnotes/strategy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost/labnotes/strategy/</guid>
      <description>Execution Strategy (Optional Reading) In a nutshell, we want our operator to start up a pod, running a busybox image for a specific duration and logging a user specific message, and then setting our Operator&amp;rsquo;s status.
We&amp;rsquo;ll want our Operator to provision our busybox pod with the necessary attribute specifications, eventually.
Our strategy to reach the end state is detailed as followed:
  I - Prototyping - Create a YAML specification for a pod which runs for a specified amount of time and logs a specific message.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
